#### Anggriawan Rayzadmiko

Bogor Regency, West Java | +6281310008091 | <a href="mailto:anggriawan.net@gmail.com">anggriawan.net@gmail.com</a> | <a href="https://linkedin.com/in/anggriawanr">https://linkedin.com/in/anggriawanr</a> | <a href="https://razd-net.vercel.app">https://razd-net.vercel.app</a>

### **Summary**

A fresh graduate in System and Instrumentation Physics, who has a great interest in Web Development and Software Engineering. Thanks to hard work, I managed to get a cum laude predicate with a GPA of 3.51. I myself am a fast learner who is self-taught, interested in learning new technologies, and can work in teams or individually. Currently I have learned a lot of new technologies over the past year and have 1 year of experience designing UI and managing social media in the Exedu Start-up Project, creating up-to-date UI designs for the web using Figma.

### **Experience**

**Erlangga** Dec 2022 – Aug 2023

Freelance – Video Editor & Korektor

- Created animation video using Adobe After Effects
- Created assets for the animation
- · Responsible for video quality according to client requests
- Created digital books with Adobe InDesign, up to 144+ books
- Initiate discussion with story writer to ensure validity of video material

**BRIN** Aug 2022 – Nov 2022

Research Assistant

- Modeled and developed a PID controller using Raspberry Pi programmed with Python and tuning it, achieve a very stable response on rocket flight
- Modeled and developed a control system for rocket VTOL that achive miss distance less than
   1 meter on simulation
- Suggested the controller algorithm method
- Assisted in a journal writing

#### Exedu Start-Up Project

Jul 2021 – Jul 2022

**UI** Designer

- Designed a google based website (Google Sites) that have more than 1500 users
- Created a website prototype in Figma and collaborated with Product Manager
- Collaborated with content writer to maximize the UI design according to the content, achieve a responsive web across any platform
- Designed attractive content design to reach the public in instagram

**Universitas Indonesia** Feb – Jul 2022

Control System Laboratory Assistant

- Evaluated practitioner's competence in the form of a presentation
- Trained practitioners about control theory in practice with microcontroller and data acquisition software

# Lembaga Penerbangan dan Antariksa Negara (LAPAN)

Jul – Sept 2021

Graduated: Jul 2022

Research Intern

- Built a PID controller with LabVIEW and implement it on rocket flight guidance and VTOL, resulting miss distance less than 1 meter on simulation
- Reported the progress and method of the controller algorithm

### **Education**

### Universitas Indonesia

Bachelor of Science – Physics – Instrumentation Physics

GPA 3.51/4.00 - Cum Laude

- Thesis Research: Design of Cold Probe Temperature Controller on Thermoelectric Material Characterization System using Microcontroller
- Digital Signal Processing Project: Speech Recognition Based on Mel Spectrogram with Deep Learning using MATLAB and Python
- Sensors and Actuators Project: Design and Build Vehicle Noise Test System for Two-Wheel Motor Vehicle

### **Technical Skills**

- JavaScript
- HTML5/CSS3
- ReactJS
- Python

- Git
- NextJS
- UI/UX
- MongoDB
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Figma
- Prisma ORM

### **Organization and Volunteer**

#### **Physics Department Student Association**

Staff
Designed attractive content to reach the public in instagram

and students

Feb 2020 - Feb 2021

# Pesta Rakyat Fisika (PRF)

Staff of Quiz Competition at Elementary School Level
Designed attractive and interactive question with PowerPoint

Jan - Februari 2020

### **Projects**

• Blogin

A blog web project that allows users to create a blog with markdown that can be seen by everyone. The project can be visited in this link: https://blogin-razd.vercel.app

Razd-net

A portfolio website to show off my front-end skills. The project can be visited in this link <a href="https://razd-net.vercel.app">https://razd-net.vercel.app</a>

# Certificate

• Belajar Dasar Pemrograman JavaScript

Dicoding, 2023

• Belajar Membuat Front-End Web untuk Pemula

Dicoding, 2023

• Belajar Membuat Aplikasi Web dengan React

Dicoding, 2023

• Python Essentials 1

Cisco, 2022

Python Essentials 2

Cisco, 2022